Guide to the Arena Stage records, 1949-2010
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center.
- Series 2: Production files, 1950-2010 (Boxes 197-588, 654-663)
  - Subseries 2.3: Production files, 1950-2001
    - K2 (2 of 2), 1982 (Box 429, Folder 3)
    - Kean (1 of 2), 1980-1981 (Box 429, Folder 4)
    - Kean (2 of 2), 1980-1981 (Box 429, Folder 5)
    - Kean, 1981 (Box 429, Folder 6)
    - King Lear (1 of 4), 1968-1969 (Box 430, Folder 1)
    - King Lear (2 of 4), 1968-1969 (Box 430, Folder 2)
    - King Lear (3 of 4), 1968-1969 (Box 430, Folder 3)
    - King Lear (4 of 4), 1968-1969 (Box 430, Folder 4)
    - King Lear, Undated (Box 430, Folder 5)
    - Kiss Me Kate, 1983 (Box 430, Folder 6)
    - Ladder to the Moon, 1951-1952 (Box 430, Folder 7)
    - Ladder to the Moon, 1951 (Box 430, Folder 8)
    - The Lady's Not For Burning, 1958-1959 (Box 431, Folder 1)
    - The Lady's Not For Burning, 1959 (Box 431, Folder 2)
    - Les Blancs, 1987-1988 (Box 431, Folder 3)
    - Les Blancs, 1988 (Box 431, Folder 4)
    - The Lesson, Undated (Box 431, Folder 5)
    - The Lesson from Aloes, 1981-1982 (Box 431, Folder 6)
    - The Lesson from Aloes, 1981 (Box 431, Folder 7)
    - Let 'Em Eat Cake, 1995 (Box 431, Folder 8)
    - A Lie Of the Mind, 1988-1989 (Box 431, Folder 9)
    - The Last Meeting of the Knights of the White Magnolia (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 432, Folder 1)
    - The Last Meeting of the Knights of the White Magnolia (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 432, Folder 2)
    - The Late Great Ladies of Blues and Jazz, 1987 (Box 432, Folder 3)
    - Leonce and Lena (1 of 2), 1973-1974 (Box 432, Folder 4)
    - Leonce and Lena (2 of 2), 1973-1974 (Box 432, Folder 5)
    - Leonce and Lena, 1974 (Box 432, Folder 6)
    - Les Blancs, 1987-1988 (Box 432, Folder 7)
    - A Lie Of the Mind (1 of 3), 1988-1989 (Box 433, Folder 1)
    - A Lie Of the Mind (2 of 3), 1988-1989 (Box 433, Folder 2)
    - A Lie Of the Mind (3 of 3), 1988-1989 (Box 433, Folder 3)
    - Life Go Boom - Prompt Book, 1994 (Box 433, Folder 4)
    - Life Go Boom - Prompt Notes (1 of 2), 1994 (Box 433, Folder 5)
    - Life Go Boom - Prompt Notes (2 of 2), 1994 (Box 433, Folder 6)
    - Light Up The Sky (1 of 4), 1987-1988 (Box 433, Folder 7)
    - Light Up The Sky (2 of 4), 1987-1988 (Box 434, Folder 1)
    - Light Up The Sky (3 of 4), 1987-1988 (Box 434, Folder 2)
    - Light Up The Sky (4 of 4), 1987-1988 (Box 434, Folder 3)
    - The Little Theater of the Deaf, 1972 (Box 434, Folder 4)
    - The Little Prince, 1995 (Box 434, Folder 5)
    - Living At Home (1 of 5), 1976-1977 (Box 434, Folder 6)
    - Living At Home (2 of 5), 1976-1977 (Box 434, Folder 7)
    - Living At Home (3 of 5), 1976-1977 (Box 434, Folder 8)
    - Living at Home (4 of 5), 1976-1977 (Box 435, Folder 1)
    - Living at Home (5 of 5), 1976-1977 (Box 435, Folder 2)
    - Lonesome Train/Hard Travelin', 1965 (Box 435, Folder 3)
    - The Lonesome Train, 1965 (Box 435, Folder 4)
    - A Long Day's Journey Into Night (1 of 5), 1965 (Box 435, Folder 5)
    - A Long Day's Journey Into Night (2 of 5), 1965 (Box 435, Folder 6)
    - A Long Day's Journey Into Night (3 of 5), 1965 (Box 435, Folder 7)
    - Long Day's Journey into Night (4 of 5), 1965 (Box 436, Folder 1)
    - Long Day's Journey into Night (5 of 5), 1965 (Box 436, Folder 2)
    - Long Day's Journey into Night - Book (1 of 2), 1989 (Box 436, Folder 3)
    - Long Day's Journey into Night - Book (2 of 2), 1989 (Box 436, Folder 4)
    - Long Day's Journey into Night - S.M. Notes, Paperwork (1 of 2), 1995 (Box 436, Folder 5)
    - Long Day's Journey into Night - S.M. Notes, Paperwork (2 of 2), 1995 (Box 436, Folder 6)
    - Long Day's Journey into Night (1 of 6), 1975 (Box 436, Folder 7)
    - Long Day's Journey into Night (2 of 6), 1975 (Box 437, Folder 1)
    - Long Day's Journey into Night (3 of 6), 1975 (Box 437, Folder 2)
    - Long Day's Journey into Night (4 of 6), 1975 (Box 437, Folder 3)
    - Long Day's Journey into Night (5 of 6), 1975 (Box 437, Folder 4)
    - Long Day's Journey into Night (6 of 6), 1975 (Box 437, Folder 5)
    - A Look at the Fifties (1 of 4), 1972-1973 (Box 437, Folder 6)
    - A Look at the Fifties (2 of 4), 1972-1973 (Box 437, Folder 7)
    - A Look at the Fifties (3 of 4), 1972-1973 (Box 438, Folder 1)
    - A Look at the Fifties (4 of 4), 1972-1973 (Box 438, Folder 2)
    - A Look at the '50s, 1973 (Box 438, Folder 3)
    - Look Back in Anger, 1966-1967 (Box 438, Folder 4)
    - Look Back in Anger, 1967 (Box 438, Folder 5)
    - Loose Ends, 1978-1979 (Box 438, Folder 6)
    - Loose Ends, Undated (Box 438, Folder 7)
    - Loose Ends, 1979 (Box 439, Folder 1)
    - Lovers and Executioners (1 of 5), 1997-1998 (Box 439, Folder 2)
    - Lovers and Executioners (2 of 5), 1997-1998 (Box 439, Folder 3)
    - Lovers and Executioners (3 of 5), 1997-1998 (Box 439, Folder 4)
    - Lovers and Executioners (4 of 5), 1997-1998 (Box 439, Folder 5)
    - Lovers and Executioners (5 of 5), 1997-1998 (Box 439, Folder 6)
    - The Lower Depths (1 of 3), 1976-1977 (Box 439, Folder 7)
    - The Lower Depths (2 of 3), 1976-1977 (Box 440, Folder 1)
    - The Lower Depths (3 of 3), 1976-1977 (Box 440, Folder 2)
    - The Lower Depths, 1977 (Box 440, Folder 3)
    - Macbeth (1 of 5), 1967-1968 (Box 440, Folder 4)
    - Macbeth (2 of 5), 1967-1968 (Box 440, Folder 5)
    - Macbeth (3 of 5), 1967-1968 (Box 440, Folder 6)
    - Macbeth (4 of 5), 1967-1968 (Box 440, Folder 7)
    - Macbeth (5 of 5), 1967-1968 (Box 441, Folder 1)
    - Macbeth, 1966 (Box 441, Folder 2)
    - The Mad Dancers, 1996 (Box 441, Folder 3)
    - Mademoiselle Colombe (1 of 2), 1957-1958 (Box 441, Folder 4)
    - Mademoiselle Colombe (2 of 2), 1957-1958 (Box 441, Folder 5)
    - Madmen (1 of 4), 1975-1976 (Box 441, Folder 6)
    - Madmen (2 of 4), 1975-1976 (Box 442, Folder 1)
    - Madmen (3 of 4), 1975-1976 (Box 442, Folder 2)
    - Madmen (4 of 4), 1975-1976 (Box 442, Folder 3)
    - The Madwoman of Chaillot, 1961-1962 (Box 442, Folder 4)
    - The Madwoman of Chaillot, 1961 (Box 442, Folder 5)
    - The Magistrate (1 of 4), 1966-1967 (Box 442, Folder 6)
    - The Magistrate (2 of 4), 1966-1967 (Box 442, Folder 7)
    - The Magistrate (3 of 4), 1966-1967 (Box 443, Folder 1)
    - The Magistrate (3 of 4), 1966-1967 (Box 443, Folder 2)
    - The Magistrate (4 of 4), 1966 (Box 443, Folder 3)
    - Major Barbara, 1959 (Box 443, Folder 4)
    - Major Barbara, 1959-1960 (Box 443, Folder 5)
    - Major Barbara (1 of 3), 1967 (Box 443, Folder 6)
    - Major Barbara (2 of 3), 1967 (Box 444, Folder 7)
    - Major Barbara (3 of 3), 1967 (Box 444, Folder 8)
    - Major Barbara (1 of 3), 1981 (Box 444, Folder 1)
    - Major Barbara (2 of 3), 1981 (Box 444, Folder 2)
    - Major Barbara (3 of 3), 1981 (Box 444, Folder 3)
    - Man and Superman (1 of 3), 1961 (Box 444, Folder 4)
    - Man and Superman (2 of 3), 1961 (Box 445, Folder 1)
    - Man and Superman (3 of 3), 1961 (Box 445, Folder 2)
    - Man and Superman (1 of 4), 1985 (Box 445, Folder 3)
    - Man and Superman (2 of 4), 1985 (Box 445, Folder 4)
    - Man and Superman (3 of 4), 1985 (Box 445, Folder 5)
    - Man and Superman (4 of 4), 1985 (Box 445, Folder 6)
    - Man of Destiny, Undated (Box 445, Folder 7)
    - The Man Who Came To Dinner (1 of 2), 1980-1981 (Box 446, Folder 1)
    - The Man Who Came To Dinner (2 of 2), 1980-1981 (Box 446, Folder 2)
    - The Man Who Came To Dinner, 1980 (Box 446, Folder 3)
    - The Man With a Load of Mischief, 1974 (Box 446, Folder 4)
    - Man With a Raincoat - Plan Lab #4, 1983 (Box 446, Folder 5)
    - A Man's A Man, 1970 (Box 446, Folder 6)
    - Mandragola, 1969 (Box 446, Folder 7)
    - A Map of the World, 1983 (Box 446, Folder 8)
    - Ma Rainey's Black Bottom, 1990 (Box 446, Folder 9)
    - Marat/Sade, 1966-1969 (Box 446, Folder 10)
    - March of the Falsetts, 1981 (Box 446, Folder 11)
    - Marching Song, Undated (Box 446, Folder 12)
    - Marie and Bruce, 1980 (Box 446, Folder 13)
    - The Marriage of Bette and Boo (1 of 4), 1985-1986 (Box 446, Folder 14)
    - The Marriage of Bette and Boo (2 of 4), circa 1985-1986 (Box 446, Folder 15)
    - The Marriage of Bette and Boo (3 of 4), circa 1985-1986 (Box 447, Folder 1)
    - The Marriage of Bette and Boo (4 of 4), circa 1985-1986 (Box 447, Folder 2)
    - The Marriage of Bette and Boo, 1986 (Box 447, Folder 3)
    - Marry Me a Little, 1980 (Box 447, Folder 4)
    - Marvin's Room, 1992 (Box 447, Folder 5)
    - Mary Barnes - David Edgar, 1979-1980 (Box 447, Folder 6)
    - Mary Stuart, 1968-1980 (Box 447, Folder 7)
    - Mass Appeal, 1980-1983 (Box 447, Folder 8)
    - Master and Margarita, 1978 (Box 447, Folder 9)
    - The Master Builder, 1977 (Box 447, Folder 10)
    - Matchmaker - Notes/Lists (1 of 2), 1995 (Box 448, Folder 1)
    - Matchmaker - Notes/Lists (2 of 2), 1995 (Box 448, Folder 2)
    - The Matchmaker by Thornton Wilder - Book, 1995-1996 (Box 448, Folder 3)
    - Matchmaker, 1995-1996 (Box 448, Folder 4)
    - Measure for Measure (1 of 4), 1986-1987 (Box 448, Folder 5)
    - Measure for Measure (2 of 4), circa 1986-1987 (Box 448, Folder 6)
    - Measure for Measure (3 of 4), 1986-1987 (Box 449, Folder 1)
    - Measure for Measure (4 of 4), 1986-1987 (Box 449, Folder 2)
    - Merrily We Roll Along (1 of 5), 1989-1990 (Box 449, Folder 3)
    - Merrily We Roll Along (2 of 5), circa 1989-1990 (Box 449, Folder 4)
    - Merrily We Roll Along (3 of 5), 1989-1990 (Box 450, Folder 1)
    - Merrily We Roll Along (4 of 5), 1989-1990 (Box 450, Folder 2)
    - Merrily We Roll Along (5 of 5), 1989-1990 (Box 450, Folder 3)
    - Merrily We Roll Along - Correspondence and Clippings, 1989-1990 (Box 450, Folder 4)
    - A Midsummer Night's Dream (1 of 2), 1982 (Box 450, Folder 5)
    - A Midsummer Night's Dream (2 of 2), 1982 (Box 451, Folder 1)
    - A Midsummer Night's Dream, 1989 (Box 451, Folder 2)
    - A Midsummer Night's Dream, 1989-1990 (Box 451, Folder 3)
    - A Midsummer Night's Dream - Peter Brook and ATL, 1981 (Box 451, Folder 4)
    - The Miracle Worker - Blocking Script, 1999-2000 (Box 451, Folder 5)
    - The Miracle Worker - Calling Script, 1999-2000 (Box 452, Folder 1)
    - The Miracle Worker -Sign Interpreted by Eric Malzkuhn, Visual Script II, 1999-2000 (Box 452, Folder 2)
    - The Miracle Worker - Cast Info, Memos, and Tech Notes, 1999-2000 (Box 452, Folder 3)
    - The Miracle Worker - Schedules and Show Reports, 1999-2000 (Box 452, Folder 4)
    - The Miracle Worker - Call Board Stuff, 1999-2000 (Box 452, Folder 5)
    - The Miracle Worker - Review Pack, 1999-2000 (Box 452, Folder 6)
    - Misalliance - Prompt Book, Blocking Script (1 of 2), 1994-1995 (Box 452, Folder 7)
    - Misalliance - Prompt Book, Blocking Script (2 of 2), 1994-1995 (Box 452, Folder 8)
    - Misalliance, 1994-1995 (Box 452, Folder 9)
    - The Misanthrope - Play File, 1975 (Box 452, Folder 10)
    - The Miser, 1954-1955 (Box 453, Folder 1)
    - The Miser - Paperwork, Runlists, Everything Else, 1954-1955 (Box 453, Folder 2)
    - The Miser - Paperwork, Runlists, Everything Else (1 of 2), 1996-1997 (Box 453, Folder 3)
    - The Miser - Paperwork, Runlists, Everything Else (2 of 2), 1996-1997 (Box 453, Folder 4)
    - The Miser - Prompt Book (1 of 3), 1996-1997 (Box 453, Folder 5)
    - The Miser - Prompt Book (2 of 3), 1996-1997 (Box 453, Folder 6)
    - The Miser - Prompt Book (3 of 3), 1996-1997 (Box 453, Folder 7)
    - The Miser, 1996-1997 (Box 453, Folder 8)
    - Mis Ever's Boys - Play File, 1990 (Box 453, Folder 9)
    - Miss Julie - Play File, 1991 (Box 453, Folder 10)
    - Miss Margarida's Way, Undated (Box 453, Folder 11)
    - Molly Sweeney, 1996 (Box 453, Folder 12)
    - Molly Sweeney by Brian Friel - Arena/Kreeger (1 of 2), 1997 (Box 453, Folder 13)
    - Molly Sweeney by Brian Friel - Arena/Kreeger (2 of 2), 1997 (Box 454, Folder 1)
    - A Month in the Country, 1958-1959 (Box 454, Folder 2)
    - A Month in the Country - Prompt Book, June 4, 1995 (Box 454, Folder 3)
    - A Month in the Country - Schedules, Perf. Reports, Research Paperwork, etc (1 of 2), June 4, 1995 (Box 454, Folder 4)
    - A Month in the Country - Schedules, Perf. Reports, Research Paperwork, etc (2 of 2), June 4, 1995 (Box 454, Folder 5)
    - A Month in the Country, 1995 (Box 454, Folder 6)
    - Moon Children, Undated (Box 454, Folder 7)
    - Moon Children, 1971 (Box 454, Folder 8)
    - Moon Children (1 of 3), 1971-1972 (Box 454, Folder 9)
    - Moon Children (2 of 3), 1971-1972 (Box 455, Folder 1)
    - Moon Children (3 of 3), 1971-1972 (Box 455, Folder 2)
    - The Moon in the Yellow River, Undated (Box 455, Folder 3)
    - Mother Courage, 1970 (Box 455, Folder 4)
    - Mother Courage (1 of 3), 1970-1971 (Box 455, Folder 5)
    - Mother Courage (2 of 3), 1970-1971 (Box 455, Folder 6)
    - Mother Courage (3 of 3), 1970-1971 (Box 455, Folder 7)
    - The Mousetrap, 1954-1955 (Box 456, Folder 1)
    - Mr. Arcularis (1 of 2), 1950-1951 (Box 456, Folder 2)
    - Mr. Arcularis (2 of 2), 1950-1951 (Box 456, Folder 3)
    - Mr. Welk and Jersey Jim, Undated (Box 456, Folder 4)
    - Mrs. Klein, 1991-1992 (Box 456, Folder 5)
    - Mrs. Klein (1 of 4), 1992 (Box 456, Folder 6)
    - Mrs. Klein (2 of 4), 1992 (Box 456, Folder 7)
    - Mrs. Klein (3 of 4), 1992 (Box 456, Folder 8)
    - Mrs. Klein (4 of 4), circa 1992 (Box 457, Folder 1)
    - My Children, My Africa (1 of 4), 1990-1991 (Box 457, Folder 2)
    - My Children, My Africa (2 of 4), 1990-1991 (Box 457, Folder 3)
    - My Children! My Africa! by Athol Fugard (3 of 4), 1990-1991 (Box 457, Folder 4)
    - My Children! My Africa! by Athol Fugard (4 of 4), 1990-1991 (Box 457, Folder 5)
    - The National Health (1 of 4), 1977-1978 (Box 457, Folder 6)
    - The National Health (2 of 4), 1977-1978 (Box 458, Folder 1)
    - The National Health (3 of 4), 1977-1978 (Box 458, Folder 2)
    - The National Health (4 of 4), 1977-1978 (Box 458, Folder 3)
    - Nevis Mountain Dew (1 of 2), 1978-1979 (Box 458, Folder 4)
    - Nevis Mountain Dew (2 of 2), 1978-1979 (Box 458, Folder 5)
    - Night Mother (1 of 3), 1985-1986 (Box 458, Folder 6)
    - Night Mother (2 of 3), 1985-1986 (Box 458, Folder 7)
    - Night Mother (3 of 3), 1985-1986 (Box 459, Folder 1)
    - The Night Thoreau Spent in Jail (1 of 3), 1970-1971 (Box 459, Folder 2)
    - The Night Thoreau Spent in Jail (2 of 3), 1970-1971 (Box 459, Folder 3)
    - The Night Thoreau Spent in Jail (3 of 3), 1970-1971 (Box 459, Folder 4)
    - Nightclub Cantata (1 of 2), 1977-1978 (Box 459, Folder 5)
    - Nightclub Cantata (2 of 2), 1977-1978 (Box 459, Folder 6)
    - The 1940s Radio Hour (1 of 4), 1978-1979 (Box 460, Folder 1)
    - The 1940s Radio Hour (2 of 4), 1978-1979 (Box 460, Folder 2)
    - The 1940s Radio Hour (3 of 4), 1978-1979 (Box 460, Folder 3)
    - The 1940s Radio Hour (4 of 4), 1978-1979 (Box 460, Folder 4)
    - No Place to be Somebody (1 of 2), 1969-1970 (Box 460, Folder 5)
    - No Place to be Somebody (2 of 2), 1969-1970 (Box 461, Folder 1)
    - Nothing Sacred (1 of 2), 1988-1989 (Box 461, Folder 2)
    - Nothing Sacred (2 of 2), 1988-1989 (Box 461, Folder 3)
    - Oak and Ivy - Contact Sheets, 1999 (Box 461, Folder 4)
    - Oak and Ivy - Show Reports, 1999 (Box 461, Folder 5)
    - Oak and Ivy - Deck Crew, 1999 (Box 461, Folder 6)
    - Oak and Ivy - Blocking Sheets Originals, 1999 (Box 461, Folder 7)
    - Oak and Ivy - Cost and Run, 1999 (Box 461, Folder 8)
    - Oak and Ivy - Sound, 1999 (Box 462, Folder 1)
    - Oak and Ivy - Props, 1999 (Box 462, Folder 2)
    - Oak and Ivy - Book, 1999 (Box 462, Folder 3)
    - Oak and Ivy - Theater Review, 1999 (Box 462, Folder 4)
    - Oak and Ivy - Works Comp Accident Report, 1999 (Box 462, Folder 5)
    - Oak and Ivy - Revised Script, 1999 (Box 462, Folder 6)
    - Oak and Ivy - Research, 1999 (Box 462, Folder 7)
    - Oak and Ivy - Schedules, 1999 (Box 462, Folder 8)
    - Oak and Ivy - Notes, 1999 (Box 462, Folder 9)
    - Oba Koso (1 of 2), 1974-1975 (Box 462, Folder 10)
    - Oba Koso (2 of 2), 1974-1975 (Box 462, Folder 11)
    - The Odyssey - Tech Stuff, Prop and Costume Lists, The Cards!, 1994-1995 (Box 462, Folder 12)
    - The Odyssey - Call Board Notes and Notes from Rehearsal and Literary Stuff, 1994-1995 (Box 462, Folder 13)
    - The Odyssey - Calling Script, Martha's (1 of 2), 1994-1995 (Box 462, Folder 14)
    - The Odyssey - Calling Script, Martha's (2 of 2), 1994-1995 (Box 463, Folder 1)
    - The Odyssey - Blocking Script, Robert's (1 of 2), 1994-1995 (Box 463, Folder 2)
    - The Odyssey - Blocking Script, Robert's (2 of 2), 1994-1995 (Box 463, Folder 3)
    - The Odyssey, 1994-1995 (Box 463, Folder 4)
    - Of Mice and Men, 1950-1951 (Box 463, Folder 5)
    - Of Thee I Sing - Blocking Scripts (1 of 2), 1992-1993 (Box 463, Folder 6)
    - Of Thee I Sing - Blocking Scripts (2 of 2), 1992-1993 (Box 463, Folder 7)
    - Of Thee I Sing - Calling Script, Otis (1 of 2), 1992-1993 (Box 464, Folder 1)
    - Of Thee I Sing - Calling Script, Otis (2 of 2), 1992-1993 (Box 464, Folder 2)
    - Of Thee I Sing - Vocal Score, 1992-1993 (Box 464, Folder 3)
    - Of Thee I Sing - Notes, PR, and Callboard Trash, 1992-1993 (Box 464, Folder 4)
    - Of Thee I Sing, 1992-1993 (Box 464, Folder 5)
    - Of Thee I Sing - Piano 1 - Act I, 1992-1993 (Box 464, Folder 6)
    - Of Thee I Sing - Piano 2 - Act I, 1992-1993 (Box 464, Folder 7)
    - Of Thee I Sing - Piano 1 - Act II, 1992-1993 (Box 465, Folder 1)
    - Of Thee I Sing - Piano 2 - Act II, 1992-1993 (Box 465, Folder 2)
    - Of Thee I Sing, 1992-1993 (Box 465, Folder 3)
    - Oh! What a Lovely War (1 of 2), 1965-1966 (Box 465, Folder 4)
    - Oh! What a Lovely War (2 of 2), 1965-1966 (Box 465, Folder 5)
    - Old Times, 1985-1986 (Box 465, Folder 6)
    - On the Razzle (1 of 2), 1982-1983 (Box 466, Folder 1)
    - On the Razzle (2 of 2), 1982-1983 (Box 466, Folder 2)
    - On the Town (1 of 4), 1988-1989 (Box 466, Folder 3)
    - On the Town (2 of 4), 1988-1989 (Box 466, Folder 4)
    - On the Town (3 of 4), 1988-1989 (Box 467, Folder 1)
    - On the Town (4 of 4), 1988-1989 (Box 467, Folder 2)
    - On the Way Home, 1990 (Box 467, Folder 3)
    - Once Around the Block, Undated (Box 467, Folder 4)
    - Once in a Lifetime (1 of 2), 1962 (Box 468, Folder 1)
    - Once in a Lifetime (2 of 2), 1962 (Box 468, Folder 2)
    - Once in a Lifetime (1 of 2), 1976 (Box 468, Folder 3)
    - Once in a Lifetime (2 of 2), 1976 (Box 468, Folder 4)
    - One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest (1 of 3), 1972-1973 (Box 469, Folder 1)
    - One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest (2 of 3), 1972-1973 (Box 469, Folder 2)
    - One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest (3 of 3), 1972-1973 (Box 469, Folder 3)
    - Optimism, Undated (Box 469, Folder 4)
    - Othello (1 of 2), 1962-1963 (Box 469, Folder 5)
    - Othello (2 of 2), 1962-1963 (Box 469, Folder 6)
    - Our Town (1 of 4), 1990-1991 (Box 470, Folder 1)
    - Our Town (2 of 4), 1990-1991 (Box 470, Folder 2)
    - Our Town (3 of 4), 1991 (Box 470, Folder 3)
    - Our Town (4 of 4), 1990-1991 (Box 470, Folder 4)
    - Our Town, 1972 (Box 470, Folder 5)
    - Our Town, 1973 (Box 470, Folder 6)
    - Our Town, 1973-1974 (Box 470, Folder 7)
    - Our Town (1 of 5), 1976 (Box 470, Folder 8)
    - Our Town (2 of 5), 1976 (Box 471, Folder 1)
    - Our Town (3 of 5), 1976 (Box 471, Folder 2)
    - Our Town (4 of 5), 1976 (Box 471, Folder 3)
    - Our Town (5 of 5), 1976 (Box 471, Folder 4)
    - Our Town (1 of 2), Nov. 15 - Jan. 6, 1991 (Box 471, Folder 5)
    - Our Town (2 of 2), November 15 - January 6, 1991 (Box 471, Folder 6)
    - Ourselves Alone (1 of 2), 1986-1987 (Box 472, Folder 1)
    - Ourselves Alone (2 of 2), 1986-1987 (Box 472, Folder 2)
    - Pantagleize (1 of 2), 1971-1972 (Box 472, Folder 3)
    - Pantagleize (2 of 2), 1971-1972 (Box 472, Folder 4)
    - Pantomime (1 of 2), 1980-1981 (Box 473, Folder 1)
    - Pantomime (2 of 2), 1980-1981 (Box 473, Folder 2)
    - Passion Play (1 of 2), 1984-1985 (Box 473, Folder 3)
    - Passion Play (2 of 2), 1984-1985 (Box 473, Folder 4)
    - The Past, 1978-1979 (Box 473, Folder 5)
    - A Perfect Ganesh - Script/Book (1 of 2), 1994 (Box 474, Folder 1)
    - A Perfect Ganesh - Script/Book (2 of 2), 1994 (Box 474, Folder 2)
    - A Perfect Ganesh - Stage Manager's Notes File (1 of 2), 1994 (Box 474, Folder 3)
    - A Perfect Ganesh - Stage Manager's Notes File (2 of 2), 1994 (Box 474, Folder 4)
    - A Perfect Ganesh - Notes/Books, The Good Stuff, 1994 (Box 474, Folder 5)
    - A Perfect Ganesh, 1994 (Box 474, Folder 6)
    - The Persecution and Assassination of Jean-Paul Marat (1 of 4), 1968-1969 (Box 474, Folder 7)
    - The Persecution and Assassination of Jean-Paul Marat (2 of 4), 1968-1969 (Box 474, Folder 8)
    - The Persecution and Assassination of Jean-Paul Marat (3 of 4), 1968-1969 (Box 475, Folder 1)
    - The Persecution and Assassination of Jean-Paul Marat (4 of 4), 1968-1969 (Box 475, Folder 2)
    - Philadelphia Story (1 of 2), 1985-1986 (Box 475, Folder 3)
    - Philadelphia Story (2 of 2), 1985-1986 (Box 475, Folder 4)
    - Piggy Bank (1 of 2), 1986-1987 (Box 475, Folder 5)
    - The Piggy Bank (2 of 2), 1986-1987 (Box 476, Folder 1)
    - Play, That Time, and Footfalls, 1976-1977 (Box 476, Folder 2)
    - Playboy of the West Indies (1 of 2), 1988 (Box 476, Folder 3)
    - Playboy of the West Indies (2 of 2), 1988 (Box 476, Folder 4)
    - Playquest - Production Book, Prodn. Info. Stage Manager Julie Fife (1 of 2), 1996 (Box 476, Folder 5)
    - Playquest - Production Book, Prodn. Info. Stage Manager Julie Fife (2 of 2), 1996 (Box 476, Folder 6)
    - Playquest - Production Book, Scripts (1 of 3), 1996 (Box 476, Folder 7)
    - Playquest - Production Book, Scripts (2 of 3), 1996 (Box 477, Folder 1)
    - Playquest - Production Book, Scripts (3 of 3), 1996 (Box 477, Folder 2)
    - Plenty (1 of 2), 1979-1980 (Box 477, Folder 3)
    - Plenty (2 of 2), 1979-1980 (Box 477, Folder 4)
    - The Plough and the Stars, 1958-1959 (Box 477, Folder 5)
    - The Plough and the Stars, 1995 (Box 478, Folder 1)
    - The Plough and the Stars, 1958 (Box 478, Folder 2)
    - The Plough and the Stars, 1995 (Box 478, Folder 3)
    - Poor Bitos (1 of 3), 1967-1968 (Box 478, Folder 4)
    - Poor Bitos (2 of 3), 1967-1968 (Box 478, Folder 5)
    - Poor Bitos (3 of 3), 1967-1968 (Box 478, Folder 6)
    - Porch (1 of 3), 1976-1977 (Box 478, Folder 7)
    - Porch (2 of 3), 1976-1977 (Box 479, Folder 1)
    - Porch (3 of 3), 1976-1977 (Box 479, Folder 2)
    - The Price - Prompt Book (1 of 2), 1993-1994 (Box 479, Folder 3)
    - The Price - Prompt Book (2 of 2), 1993-1994 (Box 479, Folder 4)
    - The Price, 1993-1994 (Box 479, Folder 5)
    - The Prisoner, 1956-1957 (Box 479, Folder 6)
    - Project Immortality (1 of 4), 1965-1966 (Box 480, Folder 1)
    - Project Immortality (2 of 4), 1965-1966 (Box 480, Folder 2)
    - Project Immortality (3 of 4), 1965-1966 (Box 480, Folder 3)
    - Project Immortality (4 of 4), 1965-1966 (Box 480, Folder 4)
    - A Public Prosecutor is Sick of it All (1 of 4), 1972-1973 (Box 480, Folder 5)
    - A Public Prosecutor is Sick of it All (2 of 4), 1972-1973 (Box 480, Folder 6)
    - A Public Prosecutor is Sick of it All (3 of 4), 1972-1973 (Box 481, Folder 1)
    - A Public Prosecutor is Sick of it All (4 of 4), 1972-1973 (Box 481, Folder 2)
    - Pueblo (1 of 6), circa 1970-1971 (Box 481, Folder 3)
    - Pueblo (2 of 6), 1970-1971 (Box 481, Folder 4)
    - Pueblo (3 of 6), circa 1970-1971 (Box 481, Folder 5)
    - Pueblo (4 of 6), circa 1970-1971 (Box 481, Folder 6)
    - Pueblo (5 of 6), 1970-1971 (Box 482, Folder 1)
    - Pueblo (6 of 6), 1970-1971 (Box 482, Folder 2)
    - The Purification, Undated (Box 482, Folder 3)
    - Pygmalion (1 of 5), 1950-1951 (Box 482, Folder 4)
    - Pygmalion (2 of 5), 1950-1951 (Box 482, Folder 5)
    - Pygmalion (3 of 5), 1950-1951 (Box 482, Folder 6)
    - Pygmalion (4 of 5), 1950-1951 (Box 482, Folder 7)